

# **Erlend Brodal**

Game Developer









Steinåsen 17, 7049 Trondheim, NO



I am a technical artist, currently living in Trondheim. My specialties are shader development, procedural generation, and technical solutions around 3D games. I have experience in creating custom tools for artists for software such as Unreal Engine and Unity, as well as developing prototypes and gameplay for various game projects. I also have experience working in both small and large teams, collaborating with other game developers. I mostly work with 3D Environments, both big and small, while organizing the whole pipeline from Sketch to Build.

### Work Experience

#### Technical Art Director at Sharp Raccoon, Trondheim

August 2020 - Now

Co -founder of the company. My contribution is developing workflow and pipeline for 3D, shaders, animation, UI/UX and programming gameplay in Unreal Engine.

#### Software Developer at Way AS, Trondheim

June 2020 - March 2021

Programming in Unity developing a car simulator for use in driving education.

#### Teacher Assistant at Nord Universitet, Trondheim

August 2018 - June 2019

Holding workshops, lectures and helping students with game development in all forms.

#### Education

Master of Science in Games, IT-University of Copenhagen

August 2019 - July 2021

Bachelor' in Games and Entertainment Technology, Nord University

August 2016 – July 2019

## Accomplishment

- Most Innovative Game, Norwegian Game Awards 2020
- Winner of InDev Game Jam 2019

